Guide to the Samuel DuBois Cook Papers, 1949-2015 RL.11747
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Speeches, 1974-2002; 3
  - Dillard Speeches, 4
    - Gillespie, Charles A. Jr., 1984 Nov 14 (Box 8)
      Delivered to International Economics Seminar
    - Gratitude for God's Amazing Grace, 1995 May 5 (Box 8)
      The Unveiling of the Portrait of Samuel DuBois Cook and Opening of a Sculpture Exhibition by Ms. Artis Lane
    - Greater Cooperation, 1976 Jan 20 (Box 8)
      Community Leadership Seminar
    - Greetings to Alumni, undated (Box 8)
    - Greetings and Opening Statement, 1984 Jul 9 (Box 8)
      Faculty Workshop on Instructional Computing
    - Greetings and Welcome, 1993 Apr 28 (Box 8)
      Luncheon in Honor of Mr. and Mrs. Jim Amoss
    - Greetings and Welcome, 1993 Dec 7 (Box 8)
      Twenty-Eight Metropolitan Leadership Forum
    - Greetings and Welcome, undated (Box 8)
    - Groundbreaking Ceremony for the Fine Arts and Communications Center, 1991 Mar 22 (Box 8)
      "Remarks: This is a Day the Lord Hath Made"
    - Harrison, Dr. Elton C., 1983 Apr 16 (Box 8)
      Presented at Luncheon of the Dillard Auxiliary
    - High School College Day, 1981-1988 (Box 8)
    - Hinomoto Women's College, 1992 Sep 2 (Box 8)
      "Sister School Agreement Between Hinomoto Women's College and Dillard University"
    - Homage to the Highest, 1976 Apr 3 (Box 8)
      Presidential Inaugural Response
    - Honors and Appreciation Luncheon, 1975 May 7 (Box 8)
      "We are Interdependent!"
    - Honors and Awards Day, 1976 Mar 16 (Box 8)
      "Conditional Congratulations"
    - Honors Day Banquet, 1975 May 7 (Box 8)
      "On Honoring Excellence"
    - Honors Luncheon, 1975 Dec 19 (Box 8)
      "The Gift of Self"
    - Honors Luncheon, 1976 Jan 15 (Box 8)
      "Gratitude"
    - Honors Day Convocation, 1978-1997; 23 folders (Box 8)
      Speakers Include: Dr. Frank W. Jr., Dr. Samuel P. Massie, Dr. Leonard L. Haynes Jr., Samuel DuBois Cook
    - How to Keep Your Dreams Alive?, 1993 (Box 13)
    - Inauguration, 1985 Jan 26 (Box 8)
      Inaugural Luncheon for Mr. Charles C. Teamer as General President of Alpha Phi Alpha Fraternity
    - Installation of Student Government Officers, 1975-1996; 7 folders (Box 8)
    - Intensive English Program and Martin Luther King Jr.: Reflections, 1989-1996; 6 folders (Box 8)
      Sayonara Program: Summer Intensive English Program for Students from Kwansei Gakuin Junior High School
    - Intensive English Program and Martin Luther King Jr.: Reflections, 1994 (Box 13)
    - Introduction, undated (Box 8)
    - Introduction of Dr. L. Oliva, 1991 Aug 15 (Box 8)
      Faculty Conference
    - Introduction: Self-Esteem, Tragedy, and Hope, undated (Box 8)
    - Is Our Duty Unique and Inescapable?, 1990 (Box 13)
    - Japanese Studies Program, 1990 Sep 13 (Box 8)
    - MLK Luncheon, 1983 Jan 15 (Box 8)
      "Is Martin Luther King Jr. Irrelevant to Today's Students?"
    - Luncheon for Freshman University and Presidential Scholars, 1992 Oct 7 (Box 8)
    - McEwen, Dr. Homer C., 1985 Oct 19 (Box 8)
      Resolution on Dr. Homer C. McEwen
    - McLean, Dr. Mable Parker, 1981 Aug 20 (Box 8)
    - Meeting with Officers and Advisors of Greek-Letter Organizations, 1978 Nov 15 (Box 8)
    - Meeting with Discipline Committee, 1991 Apr 25 (Box 8)
    - Meeting with Division Chairpersons, 1991 Oct 31 (Box 8)
    - Meeting with Division Chairpersons, 1994 Sep 12 (Box 8)
    - Meeting with the Division of Nursing, 1991, 1993; 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Meeting with the Future Occupants of Fine Arts and Communications Center, 1993 Jan 13 (Box 8)
    - Meeting with the Living and Learning Complex/ Conference Center Committee, undated (Box 8)
    - Meeting with University Assembly Committee, 1991 Oct 28 (Box 8)
    - National Alumni Association, 1987-1997; 6 folders (Box 8)
      Includes Handwritten drafts
    - Notes on Meeting with Mayor Barthelemy on the Property, 1992 Sep 16 (Box 8)
      On Parkway and Park Commission Property
    - Notes of the Moral Uses of the University, undated (Box 8)
    - NOUites of Dillard, 1980, 1984; 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Opening Statement, 1996 Nov 10 (Box 8)
      The College Fund/UNCF and Dillard University "African-American and Jews: A Dialogue About American Pluralism"
    - Orientation of New Faculty and Staff, 1987 Aug 20 (Box 8)
    - Orientation of New Faculty and Staff, 1994 (Box 13)
    - Overview of Dillard, 1996; 3 folders (Box 8)
      Visit by Mr. Durk Jager, President and COO of Procter and Gamble Co., The United Church of Christ Tour, Includes Service Pamphlet
    - Parents Orientation, 1979-1994; 8 folders (Box 8)
    - Participants in Summer Programs, 1993 Jul 7 (Box 8)
    - Presentation of the Faculty, 1996 (Box 13)
    - President's Meeting with Office Staff, 1981 Sep 17 (Box 8)
    - President's Message, undated (Box 8)
      "The Maturing of Alumni Support"
    - Press Conference, 1990 Aug 15 (Box 8)
      "Statement on the Establishment of the Japanese Studies Program at Dillard University"
    - Press Conference on Black-Jewish Relations, 1994 Feb 3 (Box 8)
      "The Tragedy of Black Anti-Semitism"
    - President's Message, undated (Box 8)
      "Of Pride and Shame: The Paradox, Irony, and Contradiction of Alumni"
    - Promises to Keep, 1975, undated; 3 folders (Box 8)
      Includes Booklet
    - A Proposal For Improving Student Performance on Standardized Tests, 1978 Jun 13 (Box 8)
    - The Proposed Land Exchange, 1984 Mar 4 (Box 8)
      Between the City of New Orleans and Dillard University
    - Radio Station Grand Opening, 1987 May 4 (Box 8)
    - Rap Session with Students, 1979-1981 (Box 8)
    - Religious Emphasis Week, 1990 Apr 2 (Box 8)
    - Retirement Dinners, 1978-1998; 18 folders (Box 8)
      Honorees Include: Clifford B. Bryan, Harold J. Epps, John H. Hallowell, Dr. Floyd L. Sandle, Dr. and Mrs. David E. Chambers, Dr. Emmett W. Bashful, Laura J. Goods, Marcus Neustadter Jr., Dr. Lawrence D. Reddick, Dr. Arvind K. M. Parikh, Dr. Elton C. Harrison, Dr. Isaac H. Miller, Dr. Elias Blake, Dr. Hazo Carter, William D. Rucker, Dr. Geneva Handy Southall, Adrienne C. Tervalon, Dr. Thomas Pendleton Grissom Jr.
    - Reunion Luncheon, 1975-1996; 3 folders (Box 8)
      Includes Handwritten Notes
    - Senior Class Night, 1985-1995; 4 folders (Box 8)
    - Senior Class Night, 1986-1987 (Box 13)
    - Simmons, Dr. Ruth J., 2002 Apr 6 (Box 8)
    - Status and Overview of Dillard University, 1994 Mar 22 (Box 8)
      Meeting of Bishop William B. Oden and the Bainet of the Louisiana Annual Conference of the United Methodist Church
    - Student Affairs Awards Night, 1993-1997; 4 folders (Box 8)
    - The Suttons and the Gift of Self, 1979 Jul 13 (Box 8)
    - The Teen High Risk Assistance Program, 1991 Mar 16 (Box 8)
      Introduction to "Wake Up, Brothers, Before It's Too Late"
    - Thanksgiving, 1982-1996, undated; 9 folders (Box 8)
    - Thompson, Dr. Daniel C., 1981 Jun 8 (Box 8)
      Retirement
    - Thurman, Howard, undated (Box 8)
    - Trustees-Faculty-Staff Dinners, 1975-1995; 18 folders (Box 8)
    - Underwood, Bishop Walter L. Dillard Medal of Honor, 1985 Oct 6 (Box 8)
    - University Assembly, 1976-1978; 11 folders (Box 8)
    - University Assembly, 1978-1995; 12 folders (Box 9)
    - University Community Day, 1995-1996; 3 folders (Box 9)
    - Videotape Campaign for Dillard, 1996 Sep 24 (Box 9)
      "Dillard University: Priorities, Goals, and Vision"
    - Why Are We Here?, 1996 (Box 13)
    - Winslow, Vernon L., 1981 Jun 8 (Box 9)
    - You Are Willing to Pay the Price, 1975 Nov 13 (Box 9)
    - Young, Mrs. Andrew J., 1987 May 31 (Box 9)
      Birthday Luncheon
  - Professional Speeches, 5
    - Academic Excellence For What?, undated (Box 9)
    - Achievement Week Program, 1978 Nov 12 (Box 9)
      "When Your Dream Dies"
    - Acts 15:1- 29, 1989 April 30 (Box 9)
    - African Heritage Studies Association, 1989 Apr 27 (Box 9)
      "The Role and Future of Historically Black Colleges"
    - A Humanistic Vision and Commitment, undated (Box 9)
    - Alcee Fortier Senior High School, 1977 May 26 (Box 9)
      "Waste, Want, and Opportunity"
    - Alcorn State University Commencement Address, 1992 May 9 (Box 9)
      "If That Light Within You Be Dark, Oh What A Darkness!"
    - Alexis De Tocqueville Society Dinner, 1990 Jun 28 (Box 9)
      "Dr. Charles C. Teamer: A Tribute to Humanistic Greatness"
    - Alton Hornsby, Jr., Lecture, 2000-2001 (Box 13)
    - America's Continuing Racial Dilemma: Hope and Despair, 1995 Jan 18 (Box 9)
      President's Lecture Series
    - American Political Science Association, 1977-1987; 6 folders (Box 9)
    - The American Political Tradition on Human Rights, undated (Box 9)
      "On Human Rights"
    - Annual Christmas Dinner, 1996 Dec 2 (Box 9)
    - Annual UNCF Kick-Off Luncheon, 1991 Apr 30 (Box 9)
      "Black Colleges, Dreams, and Hopes"
    - 43rd Annual Conference of the NAC and 31st Annual Meeting of NPAC, 1989 Feb 17 (Box 9)
      "Black Colleges: Instruments and Servants of the American Dream"
    - Annual Meeting of the Southern Sociological Society, 1992 Apr 10 (Box 9)
      "Dr. Daniel C. Thompson and the Intellectual Tradition of Black Colleges and Universities"
    - As Howard Thurman Said, 1983 Apr 20 (Box 9)
    - Assensoh, Dr. A. B., undated (Box 9)
    - Asia Baptist Church, 1993 Jan 7 (Box 9)
      "Press Conference for Mrs. Shirley Cottles"
    - Athletic Recognition Day, 1987 Nov 8 (Box 9)
      "Charge to Student Athletes: Be Role Models"
    - The Atlanta Tragedy, 1981 Mar 17 (Box 9)
      Delivered at Special Program in Memory of the Victims of the Atlanta Tragedy
    - The Association for the Study of African-American Life and History (ASALH), 2001 Sept 29 (Box 9)
      Includes Handwritten Notes and Correspondence
    - Baccalaureate, 1971 May 29 (Box 9)
      "The Vision of Relevance and the Relevance of Vision in Black Higher Education"
    - Baccalaureate: Nebraska University, 1991 May 18 (Box 9)
      "What Will You Do With Your Life?"
    - Barthelemy, Mayor Sidney, 1988 Jan 14 (Box 9)
    - Benediction, 1984 Oct 4 (Box 9)
      UNCF Fortieth Anniversary Dinner
    - Bennett Jr., Dr. Lerone, 1980 Mar 2 (Box 9)
    - Beyond Tragedy, 1982; 3 folders (Box 9)
    - Biblical Passages and References, undated (Box 9)
    - The Bicentennial and American Blacks, 1976; 3 folders (Box 9)
    - The Bicentennial of the French Revolution, 1989 Sep 24 (Box 9)
    - Biennial Convention, 1992 Oct 29 (Box 9)
      "Blacks and Jews Together: The Continuing Struggle Against the Twin Tragedies of Racism and Anti-Semitism"
    - The Black Church, 1976, 1992; 2 folders (Box 9)
      "The Encounter Between the Good News of the Gospel and the Bad News of History and Experience", Delivered at the Black Church in America Conference
    - Black Colleges and Academic Excellence, 1986, undated; 3 folders (Box 9)
    - Black Colleges and the American Dream, 1979-1984; 5 folders (Box 9)
    - Black College Conference, 1976 Apr 22 (Box 9)
      "The Socio-Ethical Role and Responsibility of the Black College Graduate"
    - The Black College Fund, 1976, 1995, undated; 3 folders (Box 9)
    - 3 folders, 1980-1984; 4 folders (Box 9)
    - Black Colleges, Integration, and Democracy, 1979 Oct 5 (Box 9)
    - Black Colleges: Instruments and Servants of the American Dream, 1989 Feb 17 (Box 9)
    - Black Collegian Luncheon, 1990 Nov 25 (Box 9)
      "The need for Black Males in the Education of Our Youth"
    - Black Colleges For What?, 1976-1980; 8 folders (Box 9)
    - Blacks and the Future of the American Political System, 1997 Apr 12-13 (Box 9)
      "The Union of Hope and Despair"
    - Black History Month, 1997 Feb 20 (Box 9)
      "African Americans and the Civil Rights Movement: A Reappraisal"
    - The Black Man the American Political System, 1970 Jun 11-12 (Box 9)
      "Obligation, Resistance, and Hope" Duke University
    - Black Methodist Related Colleges, 1975 Jun 23 (Box 9)
    - Black Social Scientists, Humanists, and the Struggle for Justice for Black People, 1980 Feb 22 (Box 9)
    - Blake, Dr. Elias, 1987 Sep 16 (Box 9)
    - Board of Directors, 1979 Sep 14 (Box 9)
      "The Future Role of the Traditionally Black Colleges"
    - Brodie, Dr. H. Keith H., 1991 Jun 11 (Box 9)
      Duke Club of New Orleans
    - Brotherhood, 1977 Feb 20 (Box 9)
      "Racism, the Christian Faith, and the Beloved Community"
    - The Brown Decision, 1979, 1984; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - But For the Grace of God, 2004,2000's, undated; 3 folders (Box 9)
    - California-Nevada Annual Conference, 1976 Jun 18 (Box 9)
      "The Vision of Academic Excellence"
    - Camphor Memorial United Methodist Church, 1984 Feb 12 (Box 9)
      "How Deep Are Our Roots"
    - Carter, Dr. Hazo, 1987 Sep 16 (Box 9)
      Commemorative Dinner
    - Celebration, Justice, and the Unfinished Task of America, 1992 Dec 20 (Box 9)
    - Centenary College Convocation, 1981 Feb 4 (Box 9)
      "Human Rights, Social Justice, and the Beloved Community"
    - Challenges of the 80's and the Beloved Community, 1981 Apr 24 (Box 9)
    - Chambers, Dr. David E., 1987 Sep 13 (Box 9)
      "The Church and the Kingdom Not of This World"
    - Charge to Student Athletes, 1987 Nov 8 (Box 9)
    - Chicago Reception, 1984 Apr 10 (Box 9)
    - Christmas, 1978-1991; 3 folders (Box 9)
    - The Christian Century, 1995 (Box 9)
      Includes Printed Article
    - Christian Higher Education, 1984 Jun 1 (Box 9)
      "Christian Higher Education, United Methodist-Related Black Colleges, and the American Dream"
    - Christian Humanism, 1988 Oct 27 (Box 9)
    - Christian Love-the Highest and Best Gift, undated (Box 9)
    - The Church and the Beloved Community, 1977, 1989; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Church-College Relationship, 1980 May 1 (Box 9)
      "The Meaning and Implications of Church-College Relationships, From the College Perspective: Responsibilities and Expectations"
    - The Church and Human Rights, undated (Box 9)
    - The Church, Its Institutions, and the Kingdom not of This World, 1978, 1987; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - The Church Related Black College: Ambiguous Past and Uncertain Future, undated (Box 9)
    - Church-Relatedness, 1988 Jan 28 (Box 9)
      "What Do Our Colleges Expect of the Church"
    - City-Wide Conference on Aids and the African American Community, 1990 Apr 25 (Box 9)
      "The Aids Crisis: An American Tragedy"
    - The Civil Rights Movement, 1989 Jan 16 (Box 9)
      "The Civil Rights Movement and Dr. Martin Luther King Jr."
    - Civil Rights Progress: From Hope to Despair, 1989 Nov 5 (Box 9)
      "From Hope to Despair"
    - The Civil Rights Revolution, undated (Box 9)
      "The Civil Rights Revolution in the South and the Unfinished Business of Racial and Social Justice: An Overview"
    - Clark, Jimmy Ed, 1980 Dec 5 (Box 9)
      "Black Colleges for What?"
    - Coalitions and Social Change: The Perennial Struggle for Social and Economic Justice, 1975 Dec 11-12 (Box 9)
    - Coast-Wide Martin Luther King Jr. Birthday Celebration, 1992 Jan 19 (Box 9)
      "Where Do We Go From Here and What Is to Be Done?"
    - College Language Association, 1975 Apr 11 (Box 9)
      "The Bicentennial and American Blacks: The Paradox of Hope and Despair, Illusion and Reality, Tragedy and Glory"
    - College Teacher, 1977 Mar 30 (Box 9)
    - Commencements, 1976-2000; 12 folders (Box 10)
      Includes Loyola University, Georgia College, McCain Magnet Secondary School, Francis T. Nicholls Senior High School, Southern University, Tennessee State A&I University, University of New Orleans, Hahnville High School, Atlanta Tech Institute
    - Committee of 25 Meetings, 1989 Sep 11 (Box 10)
    - Community Leadership Seminar, 1976 Jan 20 (Box 10)
      "Greater Cooperation"
    - Conference on Jews and Christians in the South Confront the Holocaust, 1994 Apr 8 (Box 10)
      Duke University
    - Conference - Ohio State, 2001 May 1 (Box 10)
      "7th Annual Big 10 & Statewide Conference"
    - Consortium on Research Training, 1975, 1977; 2 folders (Box 10)
      "The Significance of Research on College Campuses", "Research and the College Teacher: An Imperative"
    - Convocation, 1985-1996; 4 folders (Box 10)
      Honorees Include: Bishop Underwood, Bishop Oden, Martin Luther King Jr.
    - Cook, Samuel DuBois, 1970-1989, undated; 6 folders (Box 10)
    - Corporate Volunteer Action Awards, 1991 Apr 19 (Box 10)
    - Costen, James H. Award, 2001 Apr 20 (Box 10)
    - Council for Higher Education, 1980, 1985; 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Council of Presidents, 1981-1996; 3 folders (Box 10)
    - Creative Uses of Mistakes, 1982 (Box 10)
      Dillard Day: Central Congregational United Church of Christ
    - Danforth Foundation Conference, undated (Box 10)
    - Dedication, 1974-1995; 4 folders (Box 10)
      Dedications Include: New Library at Saint Augustine's College, United Methodist Archives Materials, Fine Arts and Communications Center, Benjamin E. Mays National Memorial
    - Democracy and Civil Disobedience, undated (Box 10)
    - The Desperate Urgency of Interfaith Bridge-Building, undated (Box 10)
    - Dilemmas and Paradoxes of the Religious Issue in the Presidential Campaign, undated (Box 10)
    - The Dillard Story: An Overview, 1985 Apr 17 (Box 10)
      Council for Higher Education of the United Church of Christ
    - Dinner of the Brotherhood of Providence Missionary, 1998 Jan 11 (Box 10)
      "Is Humankind Always on the Brink of Barbarism?"
    - Distinguished Achievement Award, 1992 Nov 22 (Box 10)
    - Do We Really Believe in the Value and Dignity of the Human Person?, 1970 Oct 11 (Box 10)
      Sermon Preached in Duke University Chapel
    - Duke Board of Trustees: Prayer, 1993 Feb 26 (Box 10)
    - Duke Club of New Orleans, 1991 Jun 11 (Box 10)
      "Introduction of Dr. H. Keith H. Brodie"
    - Duke Notes on West End Group, 2001 Mar 16 (Box 10)
    - Duke Trustee Dinner, 1993 Feb 17, 26; 2 folders (Box 10)
      "My Love Affair with Duke and the World of Higher Possibilities"
    - Education For What?, 1975-1989; 6 folders (Box 10)
    - Education Today: Success Tomorrow, 1992 July 10 (Box 10)
    - Ethics and the World Order: Reflections of a Dreamer, 1981 Mar 27 (Box 10)
      Delivered at CRIA Minority College Seminars on International Affairs
    - Eulogies, 1975-1990; 7 folders (Box 10)
      Honorees Include: William E. Pullin, Herman H. Long, Dr. Benjamin E. Mays, Jarcelyn Fields Franklin, Rev. Wilmer Tracy Woodfork, Dr. Yvonne Ochillo, Dr. Robert E. Williams
    - Evaluation of Dr. Charles Vincent's Pater on "Blacks Louisiana Politics Since Reconstruction, undated (Box 10)
    - First National Conference on Minority Child Care and Family Issues, 1989 Jul 12 (Box 10)
    - Fisk University, 1980 May 1 (Box 10)
    - Florida Agricultural and Mechanical University, 1978 Jun 22 (Box 10)
      "What Should Our Educational System Be Providing?"
    - Fourth Decade Commemoration Conference, 1982 Mar 25 (Box 10)
      "Research and Scholarship: An Intellectual, Moral, and Social Imperative"
    - Fragments and Reflections on Challenges and Opportunities: The Compton Foundation and Blacks, 1996 May 24 (Box 10)
    - From Hope to Despair: Twenty Years after the March on Washington, 1983 May 27 (Box 10)
    - Full Employment Means Total Social and Individual Betterment, 1975 Dec 4 (Box 10)
    - Fund-Raising at Black Colleges and Universities, 1990 Jun 16 (Box 10)
      Annual Meeting of the Council of Higher Education of the United Church of Christ
    - Funerals, 1977-1996, undated; 32 folders (Box 10)
      Honorees Include: Giles A. Hubert, Rev. Walter R. McCall, Marvin C. Mangham Sr., Delta Hope Ross, Dr. Brailsford Reese Brazeal, Dr. E. A. Jones, Dr. Albert W. Dent, Benjamin Elijah Mays, Alvin Peter Burrell Sr., Louise Phillips Saul, Dr. Homer C. McEwen, Jarcelyn Fields Franklin, Emmett W. Sims, Dr. Mack J. Spears, Dr. Daniel C. Thompson, Robert N. Perry Jr., Daisy Fuller "Gram" Young, Orlean J. Fulton, Dr. Ralph David Abernathy, Dr. Clifford R. Bryan, Stanley S. Scott, Juanita M. Harrison, Dr. Milton J. Becnel, Dr. Anthony J. Hackett Jr., Elodie Mason Patin, George W. Parker, Dr. Robert D. Sherard, Dr. Robert E. Johnson, Dr. Darlene Loretta Puckett-Simmons, Dr. Edward B. Williams; contains funeral programs, handwritten notes and general funeral notes
    - The Future Role of the Traditionally Black Colleges, 1979 Sep 14 (Box 10)
      Delivered at the meeting of the Board of Directors of the Council for Financial Aid to Education
    - Future of New Orleans Symposium, 1983 Oct 4 (Box 10)
    - Gammon Theological Seminary, 1990 Dec 4 (Box 10)
      "Benjamin E. Mays and the Struggle for Social Justice and Racial Equality"
    - George W. Carver High School, 1986 Apr 17 (Box 10)
      "Academic Excellence and What Will You Do With Your Life?"
    - Giving: A Theology of Stewardship, 1982 May 20 (Box 10)
    - Glapion, Gail, 1985 Jan 14 (Box 10)
      Induction Ceremony
    - God's Minute, undated (Box 10)
    - Governor Clinton and Senator Gore, 1992 Oct 16 (Box 10)
      Democratic Nominees; Not Delivered
    - Graduate Banquet, Ohio State, 1993 Nov 8 (Box 10)
    - Gratitude, 1976 Jan 15 (Box 10)
      Honors Luncheon
    - Gratitude for God's Amazing Grace, 1995 May 5 (Box 10)
    - Greetings, 1975-1996, undated; 11 folders (Box 10)
    - Greetings and Gratitude, 1977-1996; 19 folders (Box 10)
    - Greetings and Thanks, 1975 Apr 20 (Box 10)
      New Orleans District Conference of the United Methodist Church
    - Greetings and Welcome, 1975-1986; 20 folders (Box 10)
    - Greetings and Welcome, 1987-1996, undated; 29 folders (Box 11)
    - Harvard University Conference, 2007 Oct 6-7 (Box 11)
      "Prepared for 'The Future of Religious Colleges'"
    - Haven Methodist Church, 1980 Jun 29 (Box 11)
      Men's Day; "Is Forgiveness the Heart of the Christian Faith?"
    - Hayes, Dr. Robert E. Sr., 1986 Sep 16 (Box 11)
      "A Resolution of Appreciation to Dr. Robert E. Hayes Sr."
    - Heck Chapel, 1991 Sep 8 (Box 11)
      "Our Fleeting But Eternal Moment"; Includes Flight Itinerary and service pamphlets
    - The Heritage Festival, 1996 Apr 28 (Box 11)
    - Higher Education and Black Liberation, undated (Box 11)
    - Holocaust Memorial Program, 1997 May 4 (Box 11)
    - Homage to Excellence, 1976 Jan 31 (Box 11)
      Founder's Day Banquet
    - Homage to the Highest, 1974 Oct 12 (Box 11)
      Dedication to St. Augustine's College Library
    - Homecoming, 1976 Nov 14 (Box 11)
      "A Man Named Bennie Mays"
    - Hope in the Midst of Tragedy, undated (Box 11)
    - Hope in Tragedy, undated (Box 11)
    - How Big Are You?, 1973-1983; 3 folders (Box 11)
    - How Deep Are Your Roots?, 1983,1984; 2 folders (Box 11)
    - How Good Is Our Goodness?, 1984 Apr 29 (Box 11)
    - Human Rights and American Foreign Policy, undated (Box 11)
      Contains Notes
    - Human Rights, Social Justice, and the Beloved Community, 1979, 1981; 2 folders (Box 11)
      Illinois Sesquicentennial Convocation; Centenary College Convocation
    - Human Unity, Diversity, and the Beloved Community, undated (Box 11)
    - If That Light Within You Be Dark, Oh What A Darkness!, 1982-1992; 5 folders (Box 11)
    - I Love Ohio State University, 1980 Nov 3 (Box 11)
    - Integration, Democracy, and Black Colleges, 1979 Oct 5 (Box 11)
      UNCF Media Seminar
    - Integrity and Higher Education, undated (Box 11)
    - Introduction of Dr. Gardner C. Taylor, 1991,1993; 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Introduction: Self-Esteem, Tragedy, and Hope, 1991 Mar 16 (Box 11)
    - Is the South the Land of New Opportunity for Blacks?, 1976 May 10 (Box 11)
    - Justice and Leadership: The Role of Historically Black Colleges and Universities, 1991 Jan 30 (Box 11)
      Delivered in Osaka Japan